amateursonline.com 2010-12-12

# Amateur Sex and Free Porn Site at AmateursOnline.com. Homemade Adult Amateur videos and pictures uploaded daily.

Introduction

In this statement we set out how we deal with the personal data we obtain via this website. 

The use of the Amateurs Online website(s) and/or FUX software and any FUX services and information (collectively, the "Website") provided by FUX Ltd. ("FUX") are subject to the provisions of this Privacy Statement, including any amendments or updates hereto. This Privacy Statement is incorporated into and is subject to the Terms of Service of FUX (here). If you do not agree to this Privacy Statement, please do not use the Website. 

General

FUX takes your privacy seriously. We gather certain types of information about our users and we want to help you understand the terms related to the collection and use of the information which we collect. This Privacy Statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and what choices you have regarding the collection of such information. 

BY USING, ACCESSING OR DOWNLOADING THE WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS HEREUNDER DESCRIBED), ALL IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH HEREUNDER. FUX reserves the right to amend this Privacy Statement at any time and without notice, and it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Statement for any changes. Your use of the Website following any amendment of this Privacy Statement will signify your assent to and acceptance of its revised terms.

Please note that any video, image, or other content posted at the direction of users onto the Website becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Statement. 

Collected data

When you submit personally identifiable information to us through the use of certain features on the Website or by registering on this Website, viewing or uploading video content or participating in a discussion or making inquires on this Website, you may be asked to provide your first and last name, (email) address, username and a password, banking and payment information. We use this information for the following purposes:

  * to fulfill your requests for viewing video content, programs, and the rendering and billing of our services;
  * to operate and improve the features offerings and content presented to you by FUX;
  * to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries; 
  * to conduct research about your use of the Website; 
  * to help offer you other products, programs, or services that may be of interest;
  * providing information on content and services offered by us and other companies, selected by you on the basis of your personal preferences; in case you do not wish to receive this information, you can contact the customer service at [customer@amateursonline.com](mailto:customer@amateursonline.com)
  * providing of data to third parties if required to do so by law or respond to a court order.

Please note that FUX may use your personally identifiable information to present offers to you on behalf of business partners and advertisers. However, while FUX's business partners and advertisers may receive aggregate data about FUX�s users, any personally identifiable information of yours will not be shared with third parties unless you have consented to the sharing of this information.   
Apart from this, we may ask you to provide information on your profession, position, age and personal interests. We use these data to gain a better insight into our customers and users and in order to further develop our services and Website and adapt it to your personal preferences.  
Finally, we record information (including the IP-address used) for the purpose of collecting and analysing user statistics and for the protection of our Website. 

Cookies

On our Website, we may use cookies that are saved by your browser on your computer. Cookies can be used in the ordering process to save information on your orders. They also save information (such as the configurations of your pc and preferences indicated by you) so as to facilitate the next visit to our Website. These data do not contain any information on your name, address or other personal data, such as credit card information that you may have provided. You can configure your browser in such a way that you do not receive cookies during your visit to our Website. If cookies are disabled, however, you may not be able to use all the features of our Website, or may be denied access to parts of the Website. 

Transfer of the company

In case of the further growth and development of FUX Ltd., it is possible that one or more divisions or assets of the company are transferred to a third party. In such a case, the data of our users and customers will also be transferred, in which case the information could become subject to a different privacy policy. 

Transfer to countries outside the EU

For technical and operational reasons, it may be necessary to transfer your data to (servers of) affiliated companies in the United States or other countries outside Europe, in which the regulations on privacy protection may not offer the same measure of protection as the existing regulations in the European Union. We will, however, always take appropriate measures in order to guarantee proper protection of your personal data. 

Third Party Ad Servers

FUX or its advertisers may use other companies known as third party ad servers to help present advertisements online in connection with the Website. These third party ad servers may use cookies or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies, not FUX's. 

Security

FUX has implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect and safeguard the personally identifiable information under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss. All our personnel that have access to, and are associated with the processing of your personally identifiable information, are obligated to respect the confidentiality of the information. 

Accessing and updating your data

In case you want to know which data we have recorded of which you are the data subject, or if you want to change your data, please contact our customer service at [customer@amateursonline.com](mailto:customer@amateursonline.com). Please note that deletion of your personally identifiable information from FUX� database will not prevent FUX from using gathered anonymous information. 

Questions

In case you have any further questions on this Privacy Statement or on our privacy policy, please send an email to our customer service at [customer@amateursonline.com](mailto:customer@amateursonline.com). 

Effective date last modification 

This Privacy Statement was last modified 1st September, 2007. 

Copyright © 2007 FUX Ltd.
